<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NoBS</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="whatText">A world where there is no corporate bullshit,
        a world where we all know what we are buying. That’s the world that noBS ratings wants. \n\n
        Our rating system gives the power back to consumers by providing them with information
        about the social and ethical impact of the businesses they support</string>
    <string name="whoText">
        We were formed over the 15/16 summer as we went through the Live the Dream social entrepreneurship accelerator program.
        At our core is the Nobs community, the changemakers that use our ratings. \n\n
        The core team is a bunch of university students that share our passion to eliminate the bullshit!
    </string>
    <string name="WhoWeAre">
        <u>Who We Are</u>
    </string>

    <string name="WhatWeDo">
        <u>Our Mission</u>
    </string>

    <string name="Members">
        <u>Members</u>
    </string>

    <string name="titleTextSize">
        16sp
    </string>

    <string name="what_we_do_intro">
        Empowering people to make purchases that align with their values and in turn, encourage businesses to align their processes with these values to create a better world.
    </string>

    <string name="why_are_we_doing_text">
        We want a world with NO Bullshit- NO child labour, NO pollution, NO inequality. \n\nEveryone has power to create this better world with businesses they choose to support. \n\nBy providing a convenient way for everyone to understand how their purchase impacts society, we empower people to create a better world one purchase at a time.
    </string>

    <string name="the_five_pillars">
        <u>The Five Pillars</u>
    </string>

    <string name="how_we_do_it">
        <u>How We Do it?</u>
    </string>

    <string name="one_text">
        Businesses go through a rating interview to \ncollect information about their practices
    </string>

    <string name="two_text">
        Businesses provide supporting documents to verify\ninformation provided in the interview
    </string>

    <string name="three_text">
        Information is inputted to our algorithm in\norder to produce the NoBS rating
    </string>
</resources>
